Mireya Garza

Houston, TX | mire.garza98@gmail.com

Summary

I have had a lot of community service experience and have grown to excel in many traits. Through these services and experiences, I have gained a lot of patience with customers and children, a very good work ethic, and very good people skills. I believe my work as an instructor and volunteering experience will prove helpful in a team problem-solving environment.

Skills

Technical: Photoshop, Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint

Web Development: uhclspiritsquad.github.io and katnapper98.github.io **Programming Languages:** Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Languages: Fluent Spanish

Work Experience

Intern Tietronix Software

(January 2018 - June 2018)

• Front-end development

• Web application testing

Student Mentor

University of Houston-Clear Lake- Houston, TX

(January 2017 - Present)

- Help students become familiar with topics discussed in class
- Plan and organize workshop events
- Help students become familiar with University resources

Swim instructor

Lobo Gymnastics- Houston, TX

(June 2016 - August 2016)

- Create lesson plans for different classes
- discipline and keep students engaged in class
- lifeguard duty

Volunteer Experience

Teal Run Swim Team- Houston, TX

(June 2015 to August 2015)

- Help children with swimming instruction
- Give friendly and instructional attention to various children
- Help out at swim events

Houston Humane Society- Houston, TX

(May 2014 to August 2014)

- Oversaw adoptions and well-being of animals
- Cleaned and fed pens
- Spoke to customers interested in adopting

Education

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

University of Houston-Clear Lake (august 2015 - Present) GPA: 3.378